<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>IO:E::</title>
    <link>https://ioerr.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IO:E::</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>[MixedRGB](https://github.com/mixedrgb) - [Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:48:41 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ioerr.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>https://ioerr.dev/logo.jpg</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Set Url</title>
      <link>https://ioerr.dev/posts/git-set-url/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:48:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ioerr.dev/posts/git-set-url/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1 id="ah-frick-here-we-go-again">Ah frick, here we go again</h1>
<p>I was having an issue pushing to a Git repository. It was saying &ldquo;remote
not found,&rdquo; but clearly it exists as I&rsquo;m able to push to it with the CLI git
(I was using Visual Studio Code&rsquo;s built-in Git function). The debug log
was very unhelpful, so I did a little bit of digging. As it turns out,
VS Code doesn&rsquo;t even look at the <code>.git-credentials</code> file! What a big heck!!</p>
<h1 id="thonking-emoji">Thonking Emoji</h1>
<p>As far as I&rsquo;m aware, the conventional method is to use GCM (Git Credential
Manager) and VS Code will pull creds from that. Unfortunately, I had the
worst time of my life trying to sort out a problem between multiple accounts
across multiple Git instances when I used GCM. Now, this was very likely
user error [TM], but I don&rsquo;t want to mess with it when there is a simpler
solution.</p>
<h1 id="there-can-only-be-one-why-am-i-quoting-highlander-c">There can only be one. Why am I quoting Highlander &gt;:C</h1>
<p><code>https://[username]:[token]@[Git-Instance]/MyName/MyRepo.git</code></p>
<p>This one line fixed all of my woes I had been experiencing over the last
hour. I hadn&rsquo;t considered putting an access token in with the remote url, but
it definitely works. I don&rsquo;t like it at all. It&rsquo;s ugly. It&rsquo;s not simple to fix
unless you know what you&rsquo;re looking for. But I was aware of set-url and
using multiple tokens, but not using them in this particular manner. On the
up side, I can do this per repository, too!</p>
<h1 id="but-thats-useless-congratulations">But that&rsquo;s useless! Congratulations!</h1>
<p>You bet it is, and it makes me happy. I fixed a problem in a very ill-advised
way, and that&rsquo;s usually how things get done when you need something to
be <a href="https://xkcd.com/2730/">fixed right away due to more pressing concerns</a>.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft SQL Server Installation, or: Don&#39;t Install New Versions of Anything</title>
      <link>https://ioerr.dev/posts/sql-server-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 13:34:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ioerr.dev/posts/sql-server-problem/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of &ldquo;Whose Hack Is It Anyway?&rdquo; we discover the problem of
trying to install Microsoft SQL Server, version of the Year of Our Lord 2022,
on Windows 11.</p>
<h3 id="it-all-started-on-a-faded-blue-and-purple-sunny-afternoon-except-it-wasnt">It all started on a faded blue and purple sunny afternoon, except it wasn&rsquo;t</h3>
<h3 id="sunny-and-i-dont-know-why-its-purple">sunny, and I don&rsquo;t know why it&rsquo;s purple.</h3>
<p>Essentially I ran across the error code <code>-2061893606</code>, which has something to
do with the disk sector size being different in Windows 11 (apparently this
has to do with NVMe storage? I don&rsquo;t know) and SQL Server Express not
recognizing it. So I cleaned it up, deleted the cached files because I
figured there was a error with one of the cab files or something, then tried
reinstalling. This time, I got error code <code>2068119551</code>, stating <code>attempted to perform an unauthorized operation</code>.</p>
<h3 id="fantastic-i-dont-know-what-that-means-3">Fantastic. I don&rsquo;t know what that means &lt;3</h3>
<p>At this point, I&rsquo;m sweating whole cars out of my neck. I need this installed,
and it&rsquo;s hard to get ~250MiB installed when you can only go at a max rate of
~1MB/s, fluctuating between that and less than 200KiB/s. It&rsquo;s after 11pm, I
have to get up at 5am for work, and I have the following class day where,
ideally, I should have this installed!!! I don&rsquo;t know what I&rsquo;m going to do.</p>
<h3 id="but-dont-worry-weve-reached-you-about-your-cars-extended-warranty">But don&rsquo;t worry, we&rsquo;ve reached you about your car&rsquo;s extended warranty</h3>
<p>Finally, I try installing SQL Server 2019. I genetically cross-splice
several toad genes together thinking this will save the day, and lo and
behold, I is saved.</p>
<h3 id="haha-yes">Haha yes</h3>
<p>So what is the lesson we&rsquo;ve learned today? I&rsquo;ve learned that I still
love Postgresql, and that I&rsquo;ve never in my life had such an unknown
issue happen on a Linux system in my years of administrating them. But on
Windows, I may as well just drop coins in a well and hope they come back up.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Day of Class</title>
      <link>https://ioerr.dev/posts/first-day-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 22:15:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ioerr.dev/posts/first-day-class/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>First day was today. Instructor was fantastic, though I feel bad because
I didn&rsquo;t really have any questions to ask. A lot of what was covered
I already knew about from my previous stints on and off the previous several
years futzing with programming, and reading in general trying to keep up with
what is out there. He did cover about two months worth of material in the
span of two and a half hours or so!</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s only going to get faster from here, and I&rsquo;m ready for it. I&rsquo;m ready
for a new change of pace. A new direction; somewhere that I can dive off from
and <em>know</em> that I&rsquo;ll get somewhere better instead of being stuck in a no-where
spot.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermission</title>
      <link>https://ioerr.dev/posts/intermission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 18:19:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ioerr.dev/posts/intermission/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Basically this takes <em><strong>VERY</strong></em> heavy inspiration from <a href="https://gitlab.com/gabmus/gabmus.gitlab.io/-/blob/master/config.toml">Gabmus&rsquo; config</a> file for this Hugo theme.</p>
<p>Alright, that&rsquo;s enough poking around.</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New year, new website</title>
      <link>https://ioerr.dev/posts/first-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 17:02:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ioerr.dev/posts/first-2023/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Here I am in 2023, about to start anew with a fast-paced developement course!</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m pretty excited about it. Might have more to say later, maybe not. Pretty amped either way.</p>
<p>Heckin&rsquo; amped! Here we go!</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
